知道我们队伍里危机四伏吧
You got a couple foxes in your hen house, right
他们都想出去
They both want out of here.
在出去前他们不会惹麻烦的
They'll behave until then.
听着 情况就是这样严峻
Look, this is it, man.
这次根本没有推翻重来的机会
Ain't no do-overs this time.
我们今晚就越狱
We break out tonight
要不然就永远出不去了
or we ain't never getting out
这都是斯科菲尔德一手策划的吧
Brains of the outfit, huh, Scofield
他正引领你们走向深渊
He's leading you off a cliff, boys
听上去你还是这儿的负责人
Now you're acting like you still in charge.
就当我不在场
Pretend I ain't here.
是啊 也可以假装你不会用对讲机报警
Yeah, you and the radio.
有件事情我还没搞清楚
The thing I can't quite figure is
事情现在闹得这么大
with the crap storm this thing's become
他们为什么还没有杀了你
why they haven't killed you.
我们有个员工表现不怎么的
We have an employee. She's not working out.
我们炒了她鱿鱼
We fire her.
就应该处理地这么简单
It needs to be that simple.
她毕竟是美利坚合众国的副总统啊
She's the Vice President of the United States.
她当不了多久了 吉姆
And that's all she'll ever be, Jim.
你要对我怎么样?
What's going on?
去布莱克福特把斯蒂德曼找出来
You get to Blackfoot, you find Steadman.
就请你再给我次机会
Just give me a chance.
不要!
No!
律师在哪里?
Where's the lawyer?
我们成功了
We're through.
老家伙 你还撑的住吗
You okay, old man
我不行了
No!
天哪
Oh, my God!
快拉警报
Sound the alarm.
快啊 迈克尔
Come on Michael!
快拉警报
Sound the alarm!
快啊
Come on!
再加把劲
迈克尔 用力爬啊
Michael come on move it!
抓住我的手
Michael grab my hand!
抓住我的手...
Grab my hand.
求求你 别开枪!
Don't shoot please!
别开枪
Don't shoot!
我们抓住了一个逃犯
We got a 10-98! Inmates over the wall!
其他同伙都翻出墙跑了
Inmates over the wall!
还有谁
Who was with you? Who was with you?
没有了
Nobody!
-没有人 是吧?  -没有人
-Nobody huh?   -No.
快招 不然我对天发誓
Talk or I swear to God
我现在就把你脑袋拧下来
I'll snap your neck right here!
我真的不知道
I don't know! I don't know!
快报上其他人的姓名
Names. I want names.
斯科菲尔德
Scofield...
布伦斯 苏克雷
Burrows Sucre.
还有那个小毛贼
And that Vanilla Ice kid.
还有谁
Who else?
博格威尔
Bagwell man.
希诺特
C-Note.
阿布鲁奇
Abruzzi.
还有那个神经病
And that bug-eyed J-Cat...
还有谁
Was there anybody else?
快说还有谁
韦斯特莫兰德
Westmoreland.
报告 有人越狱跑了
We got inmates over the wall. Repeat.
多少人
How many?
八个
Eight
报告狱长
Warden
刚刚找到贝利克了
they just found Bellick.
把霰弹枪给我
Get me my shotgun.
珀尔已经给所有的狱警布置任务了
Pope's already given orders for all the COs to hit the streets.
你聋了吗
Did I stutter
把霰弹枪给我
Get me my shotgun!
这帮兔崽子
Those piles of crap
这么对待我
doing what they just did
他们死定了
they just signed their death warrant.
谁都别想跑
Every last one of them.
那些逃犯翻墙出去的时候
When those men went over the wall
已经做出了选择
they made a choice.
这个选择使他们再次成为社会安定的威胁
That choice makes them a threat to society once again.
正如你们所知道的那样
Now as many of you know
他们中的有些人已经被判杀人罪
some of those men are convicted killers.
我们现在要站出来
Now our job
确保整个社会的安稳
is to protect and ensure the safety of the general population
意味着如果需要击毙他们来确保社会安全
That means if we have to bring them down to ensure that safety
看在上帝的份上那就那么做吧!
by God we will do it!
同志们 这次我们可是来真的了
This time we're playing for keeps gentlemen
现在离他们翻墙而出
Now it's been at least 12 minutes
至少有12分钟了
since they went over that wall.
他们徒步最多逃到一英里外
That's one mile on foot at best.
如果有车子帮忙的话
If they've got their hands on a vehicle
可能已经逃到十英里开外了
they could be 10 miles from here.
所以大家马上行动起来
So let's get moving!
兄弟 抓紧时间
Yo come on man
我们得动起来
we gotta roll.
我们什么也不用做就等在这儿
We don't got to do anything but wait right here
让他们赶在我们前头好了
and let them get ahead of us.
我不知道这样我们还有机会逃成功吗
I don't know if we're gonna get a chance papi.
靠 有警犬
Dogs. Son of a bitch.
他们正朝我们过来
They're coming right for us.
都不要动
Nobody move.
他们闻不到我们
They can't smell us.
但是他们能看到我们
But they can see us.
你好 我现在有事不能接听你的电话
Hey this is Nick. Can't get to the phone.
请留言
Leave a message.
尼克 是我啊
Hey Nick it's me.
听着 我刚刚抵达蒙大拿
Look I just landed in Montana.
现在我正在去布莱克福特的路上
I'm about an hour outside of Blackfoot.
那幢房子
And this house
肯定和特伦斯·斯蒂德曼凶杀案有关
it's got something to do with Terrence Steadman's murder
我确定
I know it.
如果在这儿能发现任何线索证明林肯的清白
And if whatever's here can help free Lincoln
我想对你说声谢谢
then I wanted to say thank you.
有钱能使鬼推磨
Soft money makes the world go round.
你知我知
You know it and I know it.
你削减了我的竞选经费
You cut my funding
我就没办法很好地参与竞选
and I can't run a proper campaign without it.
相信我 公司内部对竞选款争议颇多
There was a lot of internal debate trust me.
你完全可以凭借演说辞竞选成功
And there's every chance that you can still win with your message
-那样这笔钱就白白浪费了...  -噢 别再废话连篇了
-and it would certainly be our loss...  -Oh cut the crap.
你还有什么想告诉我的吗
Is there anything else you want to tell me
还是说 你来这里是只是想落井下石
or did you just come here to twist the knife you stuck in my back?
好吧 事实上
Well actually
我来这儿是为了致谢
I came here to express our gratitude
感谢这些年来你为我们所作出的贡献
for all that you've done for us over the years.
你要明白这不是私人间的致谢
And to let you know that this isn't personal.
-当然你在政界摸爬滚打多年肯定能明白  -听着
-Surely you've been in politics long enough to know that.  -Look
是不是因为能源法令的原故?
is this about the energy bill?
和能源法 毫不相关
The energy bill has nothing to do with it.
为什么我觉得那么难以置信呢?
Why am I finding that so tough to believe?
我是成年人
I'm a grown woman.
不如你直截了当地挑明吧
How about you give it to me straight?
好啊
All right.
根本问题是
The bottom line
副总统女士
Madam Vice President
根本问题是你对白宫没有影响力
is that you can't effect change in the Oval Office.
而那正是我们最迫切需要的
And that is what we need the most.
发言人
Certitude.
简单地说
Simply put
你能力有限
you can't get things done.
或许你对我还不够了解
Well maybe you don't know me so well.
我强烈建议在接下去的几周里
I highly suggest that in the coming weeks
随着竞选越来越激烈 候选人开始逐一退出...
as the race narrows and the candidates start falling out
你也能够退出竞选
that you walk away
非常安静地退出
quietly
自意地退出
of your own volition.
不然的话 或许
Otherwise maybe
公司会强迫你退出
it'll be of The Company's volition.
你把衣服脱掉
Hey hey take the suit off.
在夜色中 你特别显眼
You're practically glowing in the dark.
-我里面只穿了内衣  -快脱掉!
-I only got my Skivvies on underneath.  -Take the suit off!
我会冻死的
I'll freeze to death!
抓紧
Hurry up.
-我们必须对那疯子采取点行动  -你说得对
-We got to do something about that freak.  -You got it dude.
快 动作快点 抓紧时间
Come on. Come on hurry up. Hurry up.
车在哪
Where the hell is the van?
车到底在哪
Eyetie where in the hell is the van?
给我点信任好不好
Ye of little faith.
来 来吧
Come on come on.
看 在那 我告诉过你
I told you. I told you.
你来开车 克鲁马努人
Behind the wheel Cro-Magnon.
别闹
Hey hey hey
你在那干嘛
What the hell are you doing
我在让我们不易察觉
I'm getting us invisible.
约翰 车钥匙呢
John where are the keys
-什么  -我问你钥匙在哪里
-What  -The keys where are they
我告诉过你 在树旁垃圾筒内的塑料袋里
I told you in the garbage can by the trees in a plastic bag.
那你还等什么
What are you waiting for
去 快去找钥匙
Come on come on.
不 不
No! No no no!
不!
No!
我们对55和80号高速实行全程监控
We got the on-ramps to 55 and 80 being monitored.
在171 6和53号路口设置了检查站
We've got traffic checks on 171 6 and 53.
在奥海尔和中途都有特别部门监控来往过客的名单
Special Services has secured a watch on passenger lists at O'Hare and Midway.
电话监控安排了没有?
How are we doing with the wiretaps?
所有越狱者家里都安装了窃听器
They're being set up on all the family members of the escapees as we speak.
监控小组也正在住所外围布控
Surveillance teams are being established outside the residences as well.
谢谢
Thank you.
你发现了什么线索?
What do you got?
门不是被撬开的
Door wasn't forced.
锁也没有被凿过
Lock wasn't picked.
就目前情况来看
As far as I can tell
他们基本上就是走进去的
they basically just walked right in.
我不明白这怎么可能
I don't see how that's possible.
这门每天下班后都是锁上的
These doors are locked down every night when we leave
这是第一要务
It's priority number one.
我唯一能想到的就是
Only thing I can think is...
是什么?
What?
有人故意不锁为他们开着
Someone left it open for them.
约翰 我不得不问你
Hey John I've got to ask you
你为什么这么坚持林肯来开车
why you were so intent on Lincoln driving here
还有你为什么挑了这么个特别的位置?
and you taking that particular seat?
你座位下到底有什么东西?
Now what is it exactly you got up underneath there huh?
你他妈的在干嘛
What the hell are you doing
你认为这么做就能让我停手?
You think that will stop me huh?
好好再想想吧
Think twice Johnny boy.
你杀了我
You shoot me pretty here
那他就要拖着170磅的尸体做伴了
pretty here will be dragging around 170 pounds of dead Alabama flesh with him.
你想想
And considering
他对你完成复仇菲波纳奇有多重要...
how much you need him to get this little Fibonacci vendetta of yours...
所以你最好不要扣动扳机
So I just don't think you're gonna be pulling that trigger.
不吗
No?
快把手铐的钥匙给我 死变态
You're gonna give me the key to those cuffs T-bag.
你这狗娘养的
you son of a bitch.
找找看
Get it get it. Get it.
你在找这个吗
You looking for this?
-吐出来!  -快吐出来!
-Come on. Spit it out!  -Spit it out!
快啊
Come on.
他们喝下这个
They drink this
只要几分钟就要了命
it's only a matter of minutes.
蛤蚌毒素配糖混合制剂在血液中立刻起作用
This glycoside saxitoxin hybrid goes to work in the blood stream instantly.
体质再好 心肌再强
Five minutes is the outside limit even
的人也撑不过五分钟
the strongest cardiac muscles can continue to function.
再然后
After that
就算神仙也回天乏术了
massive cardiac arrest with no chance of survival.
能通过毒素测试吗
What about toxicology tests?
放心 什么也检查不出来
Well they'll reveal nothing.
死因只能归咎为自然疾病
Death will appear to be from natural causes.
这可是很重的叛国罪
This is high treason.
你不会不知道吧
You know that don't you?
血迹未干 长官
It's fresh boss.
是今晚留下的?
From tonight.
不会超过一小时
Can't be more than an hour old.
让警犬闻过气味了吗
Dogs get the scent?
已经闻过了
Already have
长官 来看看这个
Hey boss check this out.
队长
Captain
这人就住在路边
this guy lives up the road.
白天在这工作
Works on the property during the day.
你看到一辆车停在这?
You see a vehicle parked here?
对 是的
I think so yeah.
什么样的车?
What did it look like?
像部厢式货车
Like a... Like a van.
蓝色的厢式货车
A blue van.
你就没有想过向当局报案?
And you didn't think to report it to the authorities?
一辆停着的车?
A parked car?
如果你觉得我不会亲手把你肠子割断取出钥匙
If you think I won't gut you myself to get that key
那就看看会给你什么惊喜吧
you're in for a big surprise.
我建议你回想一下上次你冲我动刀的情形
I encourage you to remember the last time you came at me with a knife.
闭嘴!
Shut up!
快闭嘴!
你们两个都给我闭嘴!
Both of you!
你们可以到墨西哥后再作个了断
You can settle this in Mexico.
离飞机跑道还有多远?
How far to the airstrip?
大概还有5英里
I guess five miles maybe.
黑老大 你的飞机最好在那停着
You know your jet better be there Mr. Mafia.
你明白我的意思吗
You feel me?
确保飞机在那儿
It better be there.
警犬布置完毕
Canine unit being deployed.
收到
Roger that.
尽量缩小搜查范围
Push past the search perimeter before we can pick up track. Over.
周围到处都是警察
They're everywhere out there.
还用你来说
Tell me something I don' t know.
你是说你对此一无所知?
You're saying you don't know anything about this?
我真的不知道
Honestly I don't.
门没有上锁 卡蒂
The door was left open Katie.
不是我干的
It wasn't me.
那是谁?
Well then who was it?
只有你和唐克雷蒂医生在晚上离开那儿
Only you and Dr. Tancredi were left at the end of the night.
值班人员确认过这件事
The orderly confirmed that.
不是我
It wasn't me.
那你就是说唐克雷蒂医生干的?
Then you're telling me it was Dr. Tancredi?
不
No...
我知道你觉察到什么了 卡蒂
I know you know something Katie.
把任何你知道的事情
And anything you know
统统告诉我
you have got to tell me.
如果不告诉我的话
If you don't
你失去的将不仅仅是工作
you are gonna lose a lot more than your job.
知情不报会让你成为同谋犯
Withholding information makes you an accessory.
如果你再不说的话我就按铃报警了!
And I will press that button if you don't start talking!
莎拉
Sara
莎拉怎么了
What about Sarah
莎拉喜欢斯科菲尔德
Sara had a thing for Scofield.
谢谢你 卡蒂
Thank you Katie.
我只想摸摸她的肚子
All I want to do is touch her belly
感受一下小生命的存在
feel that he's in there.
这之后
After that
随便让我干什么
whatever I got to do I'll figure it out.
我都愿意去做
I'll figure it out.
我就是想摸摸她的肚子
I just want to touch her belly.
我们快到了 帕皮
We're close papi.
糟了 有麻烦了
We got trouble.
这太疯狂了
Yo dawg man this is bananas.
我们必须离开这条道
We got to get off this road.
还有其他路可以到机场吗
Any other way to the airstrip
就只有这条路
This is the only road.
那我们就跑吧
Then let's just run this bitch.
谁让他闭嘴
Somebody shut him up
还是我自己来
or I will.
我们能回去吗
Can we go back
那对我们没有任何好处
That won't do us any good.
这只会让我们越来越远离目的地
It'll only get us farther from where we need to be.
那意味着我们必须冲过那个路障
Which means we got to bust that roadblock.
或许不用
Maybe not.
我们可以试着绕路走
We've got to try and go around.
来吧
Come on.
我们会从你这拿到钥匙的
We're gonna get that key from you.
我才不管你是用拉出来还是什么的
I don't care if you got to crap it out.
你有时候嘴很臭 小子
You got a foul mouth sometimes pretty.
怎么了?
What?
靠 轮胎陷进去了!
Son of a bitch we're stuck!
大家都出去
Everybody out. Everybody out.
这是为今晚演讲准备的吗
This for the speech tonight
出示证件
Need some ID.
特工部门
Secret Service.
好的
Have at it.
用力
Come on!
这车没指望了
This thing ain't going nowhere!
离机场还有多远?
How far is the airstrip?
徒步?
On foot?
或许2英里
Maybe two miles.
那我们还等什么?
What the hell are we waiting for?
赶紧跑啊
Let's move.
三只脚竞走可跑不快啊
Three-legged race over here ain't going to make it 10 feet.
我们行的 不是吗?
We'll manage won't we?
那当然
Sure pretty.
我们是队友
We're teammates.
永远的队友
Teammates till the end.
让我们离开这
Let's get out of here!
出发
Let's go!
走了
Let's go.
走
Let's go. Come on.
你就只能跟到这了
This is as far as you go my friend.
什么
What
不行 你不能在这丢下我 不该这样的
No man you can't leave me out here not like this.
我们说好了 记得吗
We had a deal remember
对 但是别这样 好兄弟
Yeah but come on bro.
你和我
You and I
我们可不是什么兄弟
we're not bros.
要不要我通知他们你和警察的事情
And I don't think you want me telling the guys what I know.
滚开
Now walk.
我们有麻烦了
We got trouble pretty.
走 快走
Go! Go!
跟上
Come on!
天呐
Oh my God!
现在怎么办
Now what?
走不了了
What do we do now Michael?
我真不敢相信
I don't believe this.
怎么办
What now
长官 检查完毕 未发现目标
This area clear. Negative contact.
又回来了 又回来了
It's coming back y'all it's coming back!
注意隐蔽
Make yourself small.
像这样我们根本走不了2英里
There's no way we are gonna make two miles like this.
特别上面还有这么大只鸟
Especially with that bird up there.
如果想想办法说不定可以
We are if I got something to do with it.
打搅一下
Excuse me.
有什么能帮你的吗
What can I do for you?
我正想问同样的问题呢
Sort of was gonna ask you the same question.
我白天负责瞭望塔
I run the tower during the day.
日落后这儿就不许通航了
There's no traffic allowed here after sundown.
飞机出了机械故障
Had some mechanical problems.
需要我帮忙看看吗
You need me to take a look at anything?
不 不用 我们自己能解决
No no we got it.
不用麻烦你了
Don't trouble yourself.
我们马上就离开
We'll be on our way in no time.
你肯定吗
You sure?
绝对
Positive.
好吧
Okay.
老兄 祝你晚安
Have a good night hey buddy?
同祝晚安
Yeah you too.
那些家伙最好抓紧时间
Those guys better hurry up.
是我
Hey it's me.
我在高斯公园发现一不明身份飞机
I've got an unidentified aircraft here at Goose Park.
最好你们来看看
I think you better have a look at it.
尾翼号码是986D
Tail number's 986-Delta.
动作快点
Hurry up
大水缸
Tranquilo
就让我用小魔力来安心干活 好不好?
Just let papi work a little bit of his magic okay?
你知道你在干吗
You know what you're doing?
你在笑话我?
Are you kidding me?
捣鼓这个对我来说就像摆弄烤箱
Hot-wiring this thing is like hot-wiring a toaster.
当然 如果这中间还有什么插曲
Now if it were to be an Acura
或者是中国车
or one of those Chinese cars
那就完全不同了
that's a whole different story.
电子点火装置
Electronic ignition
电脑芯片 统统不考虑
computer chips forget about it.
不管怎样 我们快成功了
But no we're good.
直升机马上会回来的 所以动作快点
Well that chopper's gonna be coming back again so hurry up.
墨西哥怎么样
Hey yo. What they got in Mexico anyhow
你从没有去过
You never been there
除了伊拉克 唐人街和Fox River监狱
Ain't never been nowhere
我哪儿都没有去过
except for Iraq Chi-Town and Fox River.
你看什么看?
What you looking at?
听着
Look man
有没有个地方可以容你安个家?
is it a good place where you can have a family?
那儿有很多家庭
Lots of families down there
据我所知
so I hear.
你知道我在说什么吗
Man you know what I'm talking about.
能给一个黑人
For a black man
给一个美国人安家
an American man with a family.
这就是你计划?
So that's the plan huh?
让他们去墨西哥找你?
They're gonna meet you down in Mexico?
是啊 比不见他们更糟糕
Yeah it's worse to not see them.
我再也不能这么下去了
And I can't do that no more.
对他们来说这根本不算什么生活
Not much of a life for them.
但起码也算得上是过日子
But it'll be a life.
日子肯定会比过去的两年好
More than what me and them have been having for the last two years man.
他们是我的家人
They're family snowflake.
我不可能撇下他们不管
Ain't no way in hell I'm leaving them behind.
差不多成了
We're good.
对付这我绰绰有余
I must have done this a thousand times.
我觉得你更适合武装抢劫
Man I thought you got busted for armed robbery.
那就是他们逮捕我的原因
That's what they caught me for.
红色的是火线
Red's the juice
白色的是地线
white is the ground.
把他们接到一块
You strike them together
这样我们就能离开这
and we blow this town.
怎么了?
What?
到底怎么了?
居然发动不起来
I don't get it.
太糟糕了
Great.
真他妈地见鬼
That's just great.
对不起了
Sorry.
发动机还是温的
Engine's still warm
我在这没有发现其他的轮胎痕迹
and I don't see any other tire tracks out here.
我们肯定改步行了
They're on foot
通过对发动机热度的判断
and judging by how hot this engine is
他们还没有跑远
they haven't gone far.
最多在我们前面5到10分钟
Five ten minutes ahead of us at the most.
你在哪里?
Where are you?
瑞文奇大道?
Renwick road?
在瑞文奇和韦伯大道交界以西四分之一英里处
A quarter mile west of Weber on Renwick.
行了 瑞文奇大道在南面
Okay we've got Renwick on the south
韦伯大道在东面
Weber on the east
143大街在北面
143rd Street on the north
55大街在西面
and 55 on the west.
这些路段沿线都布控了
Units are in place along all those roads.
而且更多增援正在赶过来
And I've got a dozen more coming.
布拉德 这可比我们想像中快得多
Brad this could be over quicker than we thought.
我们已经把他们包围起来了
We've got them boxed in.
长官 我们有唐克雷蒂医生的最新消息
Sir we've got an update on Dr. Tancredi.
告诉我
Tell me.
没有任何一名员工和她有过接触
None of the staff had any interaction with her.
下午早些时候她就突然离开工作岗位了
She left work suddenly in the early afternoon
回来了大约一个小时
returned for maybe an hour
又走了
then left again.
所有这些都很反常
All of it's very erratic.
有人能联系上她吗
Has anyone been able to reach her?
家里没装电话
Doesn't have a home line
手机也关机
cell phone seems to be shut off.
警察局方面证实她的车就在住所外面
Chicago PD identified her car outside her residence.
他们正在申请 突发事件许可 准备进门调查
They're getting an emergency warrant to go in.
长官 虽然这和我无关
Sir it's none of my business
但是我想提醒你是否应给州长打电话?
but are you gonna call the Governor?
我们在谈论的是她的女儿
This is his daughter we're talking about.
队长 警犬发现了行踪
Captain the dogs picked up a trail.
哪条路?
Which way?
那条还有那条路
That way and that way.
他们分兵两路了?
They split up?
看上去是的
Looks like it.
那我们还等什么?
What the hell we waiting for?
很明显我们的政策非常有成效
I think it's pretty clear that our policies have been effective.
已经实现了连续14个季度GDP增长超过三个百分点
We've had 14 consecutive quarters of GDP growth above 3%.
减税政策正在起作用
The tax cuts are working.
副总统女士!
Madame Vice President!
彼得
Peter.
副总统女士
Madame Vice President
有很多人质疑减少石油工业税收的明智性
a lot of people question the wisdom of granting tax cuts to the oil industry
根据就在于他们看到了盈利记录
in light of the fact that they're seeing record profits.
你对此有何见解?
Do you have thoughts on that?
我们奉行的是市场推动型经济 彼得
We're a market-driven economy Peter.
对那些业务模式良好的公司课以重税
Punishing companies for being a good business model
与我们的监管政策完全不符
doesn't make a whole lot of sense to this administration.
副总统女士
Madame Vice President!
瑞贝卡
Yeah Rebecca.
谢谢
Thank you.
副总统女士
Madame Vice President
你的意思是否是说
are you saying...
如果你竟选成功就会
...if you're elected president?
如果减税政策能够带来经济增长的话 那就是的
If those tax breaks result in growth yes.
对不起
Excuse me.
对不起 那位先生?
Excuse me. Sir? Yes.
那位先生 我能
Sir can I...
他们在哪?
Where are they?
他们就在我们后面
They were way the hell back there.
可不能再让他们连体下去
This ain't gonna work like this.
我们得采取点行动
We've got to do something.
这边
This way.
快
Come on.
怎么了 发生什么了
What's going on? What's going on?
你想干吗 你到底想干吗
Guys what are you doing? What the hell you doing?
我对天发誓
I swear to God.
你发誓个屁
You swear what
我猜这可能是注定的 伙计们?
I guess it was just meant to be hey now fellas?
他很幸运我没有砍到他的头
He's lucky I didn't take this to his head.
你砍了他的
You cut his...
你砍断了他的
你 你砍断了他的
You cut his...
苏克雷 闭嘴
Sucre shut up.
有人吗
Hello.
里面有人吗
Hello!
快 我们走
Come on let's go.
我们不能就这样把他丢下...
We can't leave him to just like...
你想留在这儿 随便你
You want to stay here? Be my guest.
我是狐狸河监狱的狱长亨利·珀尔
Yes this is Warden Henry Pope at Fox River Penitentiary.
我需要和州长谈谈
I need to speak with the Governor.
什么事?
Yes?
州长 我很抱歉来打搅你 但是
Governor I'm sorry to bother you
-发生了件事...  -你在收看这个吗?
-but there's been an...  -Are you watching this?
看什么?
Watching what?
我建议你现在打开电视 狱长
I suggest you turn on your TV Warden.
在华盛顿医疗中心的医生已经证实
Doctors at Washington Medical Center have corroborated
米尔斯总统45分钟前已被紧急监护起来
that President Mills was admitted into emergency care here a little more than 45 minutes ago.
据主治医生介绍 米尔斯总统突发严重心肌梗塞
In the chief surgeon's words President Mills suffered massive cardiac arrest
医生虽尽力抢救但还是无法回天
doctors were unable to revive him.
华盛顿医疗中心的消息是官方消息
The news out of Washington Medical Center is official now.
现任美国总统 理查德·米尔斯已经辞世
The President of the United States Richard Mills is dead.
根据宪法 副总统雷诺兹
And keeping with protocol Vice President Reynolds
正在一保密地方宣誓就任美国第46任总统
is in an undisclosed location being sworn in as the 46th president...
我会忠实地履行美国总统一职
"I will faithfully execute the office of President of the United States "
尽我所能 保持 保护
"and will to the best of my ability preserve protect"
并捍卫美利坚合众国宪法
"and defend the Constitution of the United States."
我宣布你继任为美国第46任总统
I hereby recognize you as the 46th president of this country.
请原谅 今晚我还有很多工作要做
And now if you'll excuse me I have a lot to attend to tonight.
谢谢大家
Thank you all.
你不是说我搞不定吗
And you said I couldn't get things done.
副总统女士 或许我们可以坐下来谈谈如何进一步发展
Madam Vice President perhaps we could get together and discuss how to move...
请注意 现在是"总统"了
It is "President" now madam
你得先和我的秘书谈谈我的档期一下子排满了
and you're going to have to talk to my organizers. My schedule is suddenly quite full.
我想你肯定能理解
I'm sure you'll understand.
莎拉·唐克雷蒂!
Sara Tancredi!
我们是警察 我们有入室搜查的许可证
It's the police. We have a warrant to come in.
你把门打开 不然我们就闯进来了
It's easier if you just open the door. Otherwise we're gonna come on in.
报告呼叫中心 发现目标昏迷在家
Dispatch this is 15 David on scene. Roll a bus to 1616 Vanlear Drive.
很可能是吸食吗啡过量
Apartment 236. Possible overdose. Likely DOA.
飞机跑道在空地另一端
The airstrip's on the other side of that field.
还有500码然后咱们就彻底消失了
Just 500 yards and this whole thing's over.
警车没有开走的迹象
He's not moving.
我们在这每多呆一秒 就增加了他们发现飞机的机会 我们必须立刻行动
Every second we stay here is another chance for them to find the plane. We gotta go now.
等等 再等等
Wait wait.
好了 我们走
All right let's go. Let's go.
迈克尔
Michael
如果我们跑不掉的话 我想让你知道 我...
If this doesn't work out I want you to know...
我知道
I know.
我能明白
别动 不许动
Freeze. Don't move.
我们不得不离开的时候 我会告诉你的
I'll tell you when we got to go.
不行 我们必须要走了
No man. I mean we got to go.
发动飞机
Fire her up
现在宣判 被告谋杀特伦斯·斯蒂德曼罪名成立
We find the defendant charged of murdering Terrence Steadman guilty.
林肯辩护律师想出来的这个拖延时间的把戏...
This stunt by Lincoln Burrows' defense counsel
是对我死去的弟弟的公开侮辱
is an affront to the memory of my brother.
我们给死者的牙齿做了齿印
We made an imprint of the deceased's teeth
通过和特伦斯·斯蒂德曼牙医记录的比对
and compared them to the dental records of Terrence Steadman.
他们完全一致
They were a perfect match.
谁杀了特伦斯·斯蒂德曼
Who killed Terrence Steadman
没有人
Nobody.
你好 特伦斯
Hello Terrence.
我已经看到飞机了
I can see it.
继续前进 快快 警察就在我们屁股后面紧追不放
Faster. Come on let's go. Oh God.
快 快跑
We're almost there.
不 不要
No! No!
我们现在怎么办?
What do we do now?
跑吧
We run.
这边
This way this way.